bjango.com 2019-12-02

# Privacy policy

Effective date: April 04, 2018.

Bjango Pty Ltd (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the bjango.com website (the “Service”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

### Definitions

Personal Data — Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).

Usage Data — Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

Cookies — Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.

Data Controller — Data Controller means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.

Data Processor (or Service Providers) — Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any person (other than an employee of the Data Controller) who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller. We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

Data Subject — Data Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.

User — The User is the individual using our Service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.

### Information collection and use

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

### Personal data

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

  * Email address.
  * First name and last name.
  * Usage Data.

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

### Usage data

We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service or when you access the Service by or through a computer or mobile device (“Usage Data”).

This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, this Usage Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

### Cookies data

We do not use cookies.

### Use of data

Bjango Pty Ltd uses the collected data for various purposes:

  * To provide and maintain our Service.
  * To notify you about changes to our Service.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so.
  * To provide customer support.
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service.
  * To monitor the usage of our Service.
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues.
  * To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information.

### Retention of data

Bjango Pty Ltd will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

Bjango Pty Ltd will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

### Transfer of data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside Australia and choose to provide information to us, please note that we may transfer the data, including Personal Data, to Australia and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Bjango Pty Ltd will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

### Your rights

Bjango Pty Ltd aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data. Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the required changes.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the right:

  * To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about you.
  * To rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurate.
  * To request the deletion of Personal Data held about you.

You have the right to data portability for the information you provide to Bjango Pty Ltd. You can request to obtain a copy of your Personal Data in a commonly used electronic format so that you can manage and move it.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

### Service providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### Payments

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

The payment processors we work with are:

  * Apple App Store. Their Privacy Policy can be viewed by visiting [apple.com/legal/privacy/en-ww/](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/en-ww/).
  * Google Play Store. Their Privacy Policy can be viewed by visiting [google.com/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).
  * Paddle. Their Privacy Policy can be viewed by visiting [paddle.com/legal](https://paddle.com/legal).

### Merchant of Record

Our order process for iStat Menus is conducted by our online reseller Paddle.com. Paddle.com is the Merchant of Record for all iStat Menus orders. Paddle provides all customer service inquiries and handles returns.

### Links to other sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

### Children’s privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (“Children”). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

### Changes to this privacy policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

### Contact us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by visiting bjango.com/contact/.
